Number one
K-content channel.
tvN for joy.
Fifteen.
THE FOLLOWING PROGRAM IS
NOT SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS PRODUCT PLACEMENTS
AND VIRTUAL ADVERTISING.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
PRODUCTION SUPPORTED BY:
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS AND TOURISM
KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
THIS DRAMA
IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD AND ANIMAL SCENES WERE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION
Luni, what does it mean
if someone gives you a bottle of wine
and says it's from her heart?
In fact, that wine is said
to help one's love come true.
That means more than interest.
It's normally used
to express a head-on romance.
A head-on romance?
That woman definitely likes you.
CHAN
Da-reum, I'll be out of town
for a few days from tomorrow.
Could we meet up at least
for a moment before I leave?
So she
likes me?
Let's go. I'll walk you home.
No, thank you.
I need to stop by somewhere.
I'll go by myself.
But still, I should walk you...
Mr. Kang, are you okay?
Of course, I'm fine.
Why wouldn't I be?
You seem a little off.
Your face is all red.
- Just go away.
- What?
I take back walking you home.
It's canceled.
Go on already.
Bye.
Okay, I'll be going then.
Goodbye.
This one is obviously way heavier.
Same amount, my foot.
How come my own mother
cares more about Ha-gi than me?
It's ridiculous.
What on earth?
Why is a girl
coming out of this house?
Tell me. Who is she?
Why would your employee come
all the way to your house?
And what's with those romantic eyes?
I had an urgent proposal to finish.
She was here to help. Happy now?
She looked familiar, though.
The nosebleed! The big ice ball!
She's that crazy drunk girl, right?
So she works for you now?
Mind your own business.
Is that wine?
So much for work.
You two are totally a thing.
I didn't set it up.
She brought it over
saying it was from her heart.
Wait, so she confessed to you?
Well...
She hasn't said it out loud.
Mr. Kang, have this and cheer up.
Good luck.
But she sneaks up to cheer me on.
Mr. Kang!
I'll move next to you.
She randomly puts her hands on me.
Oh, man.
Above all...
She smiles at me
every time she sees me.
She must have feelings for me, right?
No.
At that point...
it's love.
What...
Love?
Love.
COULD WE MEET UP AT LEAST
FOR A MOMENT BEFORE I LEAVE?
LEE CHAN OFFICIAL
HAS STARTED A LIVE STREAM
TUNE IN RIGHT NOW!
Hi. It's been a while, right?
I have an early start tomorrow,
so I can't stay long.
I went live
because I just wanted to see you,
even if it was like this.
I can't see you, but you can see me.
There's something
I wanted to tell you in person.
I might have hurt you
because I wasn't careful at times
but thank you
for always supporting me.
That's how I truly feel.
I read in my favorite book
that sincerity eventually
shines through over time.
I hope my sincerity
reaches you as well.
Gosh, it's late.
I should go to bed now.
I'll be back. Bye.
THE LIVE STREAM HAS ENDED
DA-REUM
Chan, I'm afraid
I don't have time today.
Let's catch up later.
And I'm okay
with what happened that day.
Please don't let it bother you.
Thanks for texting me back, Da-reum.
Have a safe trip to your shoot.
I'll be rooting for you from afar.
I'LL BE ROOTING FOR YOU FROM AFAR
APPELLO
Get a grip, Kang Ha-gi.
Act normal.
Just keep it normal.
Thank
you...
Mr. Kang, did you find
any more stickers at home?
Yesterday felt like a treasure hunt.
It was really fun.
- If you find more...
- Ms. Nam.
Yes?
We're at work.
I'm the CEO.
CEO
And you're an employee.
EMPLOYEE
Keep your personal
and work life
separate, okay?
Goodness.
The doors are closing.
Wait, Mr. Kang!
Mr. Kang, let me...
What was that about?
What's wrong with him
this early in the morning?
Did I mess up again?
Excuse me. Sorry.
The CEO is going to call me in a bit.
Make some room, please.
Why would he call you?
Why else? Look at that.
The K-Wave project is worth
a massive 1.5 billion won.
- Check this out.
- Oh, really?
K-SWEETNESS
TO SATISFY YOUR 5 SENSES!
"A Dalgona keychain
that tastes sweet when you lick it."
Is this really the best
an adult could come up with?
It's a 100 percent fail.
If you carry that around,
it's totally going to attract bugs.
I hope it works out.
- What's with that look?
- Let's start the meeting.
K-WAVE PROJECT
INTERNAL CONTEST RESULTS
We took internal submissions
for the K-Wave project hosted
by the Korea Heritage Service, right?
Today, I'll announce the winner.
Since there's only one spot
for the fashion category
in this project
the choice of item was crucial.
The chosen idea is
Lee...
Min-a's Mosaic Bojagi.
- Congrats!
- Congratulations.
- Sit back down.
- Sit down quickly.
Min-a, congratulations.
This is awesome.
Ms. Min-a, please come up
and walk us through it.
Yes, sir.
Incredible!
Hello.
I'm Lee Min-a, a new hire
on the Merchandising...
- Team.
- She's nervous.
Well...
My proposed item is the Mosaic Bojagi
inspired by the traditional
patchwork wrapping cloth.
The plan is to collaborate
with Geosang fabric shop in Jongno
which has been around
for three generations.
The patchwork wrapping cloth
closely resembles mosaics
and stained glass.
I expect it to feel familiar
to international customers too.
It's so pretty.
That's all. Thank you.
Awesome!
Marketing and Merchandising
will work on this project together.
- Yes, sir.
What's that? It's so cute.
A fan of mine drew this character.
It's so cute
that I've got it all memorized.
What's this supposed to be, though?
A bear or a pig?
Good point. It has a pig's nose
- but a bear's ears.
- I'd say it's a pig.
They're looking for the styling team.
- Okay, we'll head over.
- Thanks.
- Chan.
- Oh, thank you.
I honestly don't know where you'd be
without that photo book.
What makes it so special that you
carry it around like a lucky charm?
It just...
makes me feel better.
Whenever I doubt myself
wondering if I should
continue with this career
or if people will still love me...
this book cheers me on to keep going.
The fan who made this
probably has no idea
that it became
your most treasured item.
I don't think she's still my fan.
It's been ten years.
True, so much time has passed.
Who stays that devoted
for such a long time?
I adored you for 12 years.
I can tell that much.
You are a good person.
If you tried to be
a good person so far
that alone makes you a good person.
Actually, there is.
There's one.
SE CORPORATION
What are SE's cars doing here?
No way. Just a moment, please.
GEOSANG FABRIC SHOP
Thank you
for making the right decision.
My pleasure.
Sir.
Hello, Ms. Lee.
What's going on here?
You remember we're signing
the contract today, right?
Well, the thing is...
Listen, I'm sorry.
SE brought us a similar offer first.
And their terms were far better.
But sir.
I showed you
this Mosaic Bojagi
before anyone else.
How could SE possibly know...
Ideas can
overlap, can't they?
Excuse me?
Ms. Nam? That's none of your concern.
The operations team
will take care of it.
What?
I'm sorry.
Canceling on the day of the contract?
That makes no sense.
They even snatched our workshop.
It seems they're trying to block us
from bidding altogether.
We've been backstabbed by SE
way too many times.
At this rate,
it's definitely an inside job.
We need to root them out, sir.
Are you suggesting
there's a spy among us?
- What other explanation is there?
- Listen.
I also had...
the same thought for a while.
But my conclusion was
not to recklessly suspect
my own Appello people.
Right now, winning this bid is
what matters most.
Everyone, focus on coming up
with a backup item.
- Yes, sir.
- Gosh.
The deadline is in ten days.
- My Dalgona keychain...
- Let's stop here.
But the Dalgona...
- We don't have much time...
- I'm sorry.
I apologize.
COCOTALK
LEE CHAN'S SCHEDULE CHAT
LEE CHAN'S SCHEDULE FOR DECEMBER
Before makeup today.
I'll still push through.
Is she busy?
DA-REUM
She has such a nice smile.
Mr. Kang, you should go home today.
You pulled an all-nighter
yesterday too.
Not until we find a backup item.
If SE snatches the K-Wave project
along with their platform launch
we'll lose all our investors.
Then, maybe we should revisit
- my Dalgona...
- Are you kidding me?
Read the room, for crying out loud.
You're being such a nuisance.
Young-woo, any updates
on the traditional boxes?
The wooden lacquer box makers aren't
producing any because the lacquer
- won't dry in the winter.
- Yes.
And the mother-of-pearl boxes
are way over our budget.
How about the binyeo hairpins?
They're already working
with another company.
How did it go
with the Korean paper hanji?
They refused to collaborate.
So, every single vendor
on this list said no?
What now? We're never going
to make the deadline at this rate.
All right. Even so
let's keep trying
until we find a way.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Okay.
Ms. Nam.
Where did you get this?
Pardon?
This keychain.
My mom knows the apprentice
of this master knot artisan.
She got it from her.
MASTER KNOT ARTISAN
IM CHEONG-RIM
The colors and designs are amazing.
- Right.
- I agree.
How do we get in touch?
The master is practically
living in seclusion
so even if we go to see her,
it might not work.
My mom said she'd ask the apprentice.
- Please...
- This has to work.
CEO KANG HA-GI OF APPELLO
I'll be outside your place
tomorrow morning.
Pack for a business trip and meet me.
Don't tell anyone where we're going.
Keep this strictly confidential.
"Strictly confidential"?
KEEP THIS STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL
So, is it just Mr. Kang and me going?
- Ms. Nam, hop in.
- Yes, sir.
Anyway, why are we keeping
this business trip a secret?
SE tricked us once.
They may do it again.
I want to keep this under the radar
until the contract is signed.
Fair enough. Even we don't know
where the master is.
It'd be hard for them
to steal the item.
But why are you taking me with you?
You have the closest link
to the master.
And more importantly
you're the only one
I can trust right now.
Says someone
who once called me a spy.
You can count on me.
I, Nam Da-reum, will take full charge
of escorting you around Jungsan-si.
Please take good care of it.
Thank you. Bye.
I just got off the phone
with the natural silk thread place.
We'll have samples by tomorrow.
Brainstorm some ideas
on how to turn this into a product.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Got it.
Where did Ms. Da-reum go
to find that master knot artisan?
Did Mr. Kang go with her?
Beats me. I'm not sure
about the details either.
I see.
I can't believe
we're passing by here.
Over there is where I lived.
Down this way is the market.
If you head that way,
there's a lake park.
You really do know
your way around here.
Of course.
You're practically a spy if you don't
know my name around here.
Is that Nam Da-reum...
the same Nam Da-reum
standing right here?
NEULPUM CREDIT UNION MEMBER
KIM MI-JA'S ELDEST DAUGHTER,
NAM DA-REUM
JOINS SE CORPORATION!
What is that?
You really are a local celebrity.
I can't believe this.
Mo...
Mom.
What's with that banner?
Take it down right away.
I paid good money for that,
so why would I take it down?
It will stay up there
for at least half a year.
I guess you've arrived.
Aren't you coming to see me?
I'm here for work,
so I won't be able to visit.
What about the favor I asked for?
Go to your old high school.
She can only spare
a brief time after lunch.
Got it.
Thank you so much.
I'll call you later.
Bye.
Don't take a picture of that.
Why would you even photograph it?
You are the pride
of this entire town.
Ms. Nam Da-reum
of SE Corporation.
If we go straight this way...
- Isn't it pretty?
- This...
This whole neighborhood
must be full of memories for you.
Right.
It feels a bit weird
to be here with you, though.
That's my all-time
favorite snack bar!
OUR SNACK FOOD
Wow, I used to go there all the time.
Stay on the inside.
Okay.
He's oddly sweet.
Have a seat and wait for a moment.
I'll call the cafeteria.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
- This way.
- Okay.
It's been such a long time.
Should we sit here for a bit?
So, this is your old high school?
Yes.
I used to sit right here
and listen to music a lot.
Nothing has changed.
- You're handsome.
- You're so handsome.
- Hello.
- Are you a celebrity?
- No.
- An actor? Or a model?
You're so handsome.
Do you have Instar?
Let's take a selfie.
- Right here.
- You're seriously good-looking.
- Awesome.
- So handsome.
- Girls?
- Jeez.
- I'm not anyone like that.
- You're so hot!
What the heck?
- Where are you going?
- What...
Wait. Isn't that Da-reum?
Hi, guys. Today, I'm going
to vlog myself getting ready
to buy some wholesale stock.
ASEUL-ASEUL
CLICK TO VISIT THE WEBSITE
I don't drive
so I'm taking a cab to get my stock.
LIKE, COMMENT, AND SUBSCRIBE!
This is the place I got
those strawberry panties from.
I'm going for some daring panties
this time.
I prefer to buy products
after seeing and touching them
in person.
You have all of those in stock.
HIGH DEMAND EXPECTED
BLINK AND IT'S SOLD OUT
I told you to keep it down
while I'm recording.
Why aren't you doing
any actual work lately?
I am working.
I'm telling you. Video marketing is
how you sell these days.
Wait and see.
Orders are going to pour in soon.
As if.
Refunds rather poured in
for those super push-up bras.
Hey.
I got scammed
because I was a newbie back then.
How was I supposed to know
the padding would slide to the side?
Which is why you should stick
to what you know.
Why sell sexy lingerie
you've never even tried on?
You fool.
Darn you.
Looks like I got an order.
BYEOL-A
I guess Da-reum went down
to our hometown.
What?
- Without saying a word to us?
- You're right.
Da-reum showed up at school
with a handsome guy.
Maybe it's her boyfriend.
Her boyfriend?
Who was this tall, good-looking guy?
You're incredibly popular
with those high school girls.
I bet you broke a few hearts
back in your school days.
Well, I suppose I had my moments.
As always
you're so honest.
What about you?
How were your school days?
Make a guess.
I guess you were bright
energetic...
and a total social butterfly
like you are now.
Wrong.
I was actually...
an outcast for a while.
I spent many lunch breaks
sitting entirely on my own.
That's why
seeing kids like that earlier...
tugs at me.
It's a feeling only those
who have lived it can understand.
Perhaps that's why
you're so quick to care...
for others.
Still, I have
way more good memories here.
I found someone who gave me strength.
I got through it fine thanks to him.
Who was that?
My...
first love.
Seeing how hard he tried
motivated me to push myself harder.
Anyway, I'm really grateful to him.
That's a relief.
I'm glad you had
someone like that back then.
Excuse me.
Are you here to meet my master?
Oh, yes.
- Hello.
NAM DA-REUM
KANG HA-GI
I came out
because Mi-ja begged me, but...
Just give us the location.
We'll handle the talking.
Promise never to mention
that you heard from me.
Of course, we promise.
It won't be easy.
Try to hold your ground. Good luck.
Excuse me. Anyone here?
- Hello.
Hello. May I ask
where we can find the master?
She's inside over there.
- Thank you.
Wow, look at that color.
It turned out amazing.
- Yeong-suk, grab some green onions.
- Okay.
- Hello.
Who are you?
We're from a company
called Appello in Seoul.
This is
Master Im Cheong-rim's place, right?
Oh, my. How did you find this place?
Cheong-rim! You have visitors.
Come out and see.
CERTIFICATE OF APPOINTMENT
SKILL TRANSMISSION MERIT AWARD
Master Im, this is a mockup
we've prepared.
BLENDING TRADITION WITH TRENDS
Appello is a fashion platform
that curates local designer brands.
Right now,
we're spearheading an initiative
to merge traditional crafts
with modern design.
We believe we can help
show your work to the world...
What about the manufacturing?
Please don't worry about that.
We've got
a highly skilled factory lined up...
A factory?
I'm not interested.
If you're not happy
- with the factory...
- No.
I have no words for merchants.
Get out now.
What now?
Ms. Nam, you've done enough here.
I'll drop you off at the bus terminal
so head back to Seoul without me.
What about you, sir?
I'm not leaving
until I convince Master Im.
I became certain
after seeing her in person.
Then...
I'll stay too.
I'll do whatever I can to help.
What are you going to do?
I should do whatever I can.
Ms. Da-reum.
We Koreans look out for each other.
You're making a mountain of kimchi.
How could I just walk away?
Let me help out just a little.
Should I season
the pickled napa cabbage?
Your arms are as thin
as a pair of chopsticks.
Have you made kimchi before?
It's not an easy feat.
I may not look it,
but I helped my mom
for a good few years.
- Pitch in already.
- Okay.
Make sure to coat the outsides.
- Like this?
- Spread it out.
A farmhand from Seoul
is willing to help out.
- What?
- Gosh...
- A farmhand?
- How cute.
- That looks heavy. Give me that.
- Don't be too eager.
It looks heavy.
The napa cabbages are pickled.
He has chopsticks for arms too.
- He's pretty useful, though.
- They go here?
You have chopstick arms
and so does he.
You look too weak.
- He'll be of use somewhere.
- Give me that.
Can he even lift chopsticks to eat?
EYES ONLY FOR YOU, PARK SEO-JIN
Push, push, push it away
Push away the dirt in your heart
To the beat.
Did you tell Da-reum where to go?
You bet.
She was with a coworker.
They looked really busy.
- Right?
- Yes.
Working at that huge company in Seoul
must be really hard on her.
She works at SE Corporation
of all places.
- There must be lots to do.
- SE Corporation?
That's weird. It wasn't called that.
What do you mean?
It wasn't called SE?
- Pell-something.
- What?
Pell...
It sounded like pell... Oh, right.
Appello. That's where she works.
APPELLO
NAM DA-REUM
What's this?
"Appello"?
- Ms. Da-reum.
- Yes?
Do better.
You're not supposed to smack it.
You're coating the leaves.
Follow the grain
so it gets everywhere.
So it seeps in.
Like this? Is this what you do?
You crushed all the leaves.
Be more gentle.
More caring, okay?
You care about details
with everything.
Once I set my mind to it,
I go all out.
- I'm wearing this again.
- What?
I thought the cast
would be the last of it.
Wait. The red rubber gloves.
Did you actually
wear them?
You burst into a fury and said
you had to watch your back and front
and that you couldn't
let your guard down.
Did you wear them?
I did wear them, okay?
You swore you wouldn't.
Jeez.
Weren't they nice?
Don't ask.
- Do better.
- I am doing better.
Your napa cabbage is almost...
Mi-ja!
Mom.
What are you doing here?
You!
Give me those gloves.
- What?
- Go over there
and help move the kimchi.
Give me the rubber gloves!
Okay...
Move.
Mom...
Master Im.
Please give my daughter a chance.
She doesn't do a shoddy job,
whatever it is.
With your help, she'll do great.
The kimchi looks amazing.
You bought
some quality napa cabbages.
Look at the color.
When you're done
you need to wrap each head carefully.
The more seasoning, the better.
Look at you.
You look good today.
Should I not have registered
for a group lesson too?
I can't have
all the ladies falling for me
when Mi-mi's right there.
Take a long step backward
with your right foot
and go down and count one.
Two.
Again, one
and two.
Again, one.
Arms forward, Mr. Min-woo.
Strengthen your core.
Keep your back straight
and strengthen your core.
Watch your core.
Keep your arms down
and watch your core.
That's it. Keep this posture. Two.
Again, one.
Breathe in and straighten your back.
Your arms should be up here.
Why are you so weak?
And two.
- Get back up, Mr. Min-woo.
- Okay.
This is the last count. One...
SMOOTH PILATES
- What, really?
- Yes.
Don't be silly.
Oh, my gosh.
Min-woo.
Come here. We're leaving.
Where to?
Where else?
To your welcome dinner, of course.
- I don't need one.
- Let's go.
- Come along.
- But I...
- What do you like?
- Goodbye.
- Meat.
- You're not coming?
- Bye.
- See you.
- Take this, please.
- Sure.
Oh, dear.
It's so hot.
- Ms. Da-reum. I'll take it.
- Thanks.
Where did Mi-ja go?
- Tell your mom dinner's ready.
- Okay.
Mom.
Thanks for your help.
After all I went through
to raise you...
What work do you do
that you're here making kimchi?
Mom, actually...
There's something I didn't tell you.
I...
I quit SE Corporation.
I know.
- You know?
- It's Appello or something.
I saw your business card.
I'm sorry I lied.
You were so pleased
that I got into SE Corporation.
I didn't want to let you down.
I'm not upset
that you left a huge corporation.
You didn't tell me.
That's what hurts.
Wouldn't it have been nice
if you'd told me
you were having
a hard time at school?
I know it's because
you don't want me to worry
but I wonder
if it's because you don't trust me.
Each time you keep something from me
I get really upset.
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
But Mom.
It's a small company
but they use my ideas,
and I can voice my opinion.
I feel...
like I can be of use there.
That's why I like Appello
and I'm happier there.
Then all is well.
Whether you work at a big
or a small company, all I want...
is for you to be happy.
Thank you, Mom.
Don't cry.
- Cheers.
- You too?
- How is it?
- I'll get more meat.
- Okay.
Ma'am, have some of this.
And this.
Thanks.
My Da-reum.
Look after her for me, Mr. Kang.
She hasn't worked for that long
so she has a lot to learn.
Not a lot, actually.
Just a bit.
She lacks just a bit.
She's diligent
and hard-working, though.
All my employees work hard.
I guess you have nothing good
to say about my Da-reum.
Ms. Da-reum
is an exemplary employee.
She's always so cheerful
and she gives every task her all.
She hasn't been with us very long,
but she's already been a huge help.
You don't have to worry.
My gosh. Is that so?
I thought she was kind
and warmhearted.
She must've gotten that from you.
What?
How did you know that?
People say we're carbon copies
whenever we're out together.
- Do they?
- Oh, let's clink bowls.
Sure.
You're a good drinker, Mr. Kang.
- Have some more.
- Thanks.
Gosh.
- You too.
- Thanks.
So, about my Da-reum.
Is she seeing anyone at work?
Or have a crush on someone?
Pardon?
I don't know anything about that.
I'm worried. She doesn't seem
to care about dating.
By the way
you look incredibly young.
Are you still unmarried?
Unmarried? Yes, I am.
Are you?
Then
what is your ideal kind of woman?
- Pardon?
- You said
Da-reum was kind and warmhearted.
Are you not into that kind of woman?
Well, it's not...
Mom.
Why are you talking nonsense?
Don't grill my boss.
I just wanted to know
what his ideal type was.
You're not supposed to ask that
at work.
There are reasons too.
Did I just get you fired
when you just joined?
- No way.
- What if I did?
Ma'am.
The man your daughter has a crush on.
It's me.
APPELLO
Director.
- Hello.
What brings you here?
I dropped by after a shoot.
Is Marketing busy these days?
The K-Wave project
keeps us here late every day.
Mr. Ha-gi's still here, right?
Mr. Kang's on a business trip.
With Ms. Da-reum.
With Ms. Da-reum?
To sign with a master knot artisan
from Ms. Da-reum's hometown.
They seem to be stuck.
I don't think they'll return
until the deal is signed.
We're ready for the meeting.
- Okay.
- Great.
Director, I have a meeting.
What will you do?
There's no one else here to see.
I'll get going.
- Get back safely, Director.
- Take care.
APPELLO
NAM DA-REUM
MAP TO MOUNT NAMSAN LOCATION,
ROUTE AND EVENT COMMENTS
K-WAVE PROJECT
APPELLO WILL WIN! LET'S GO!
A fan of mine drew this character.
It's so cute
that I've got it all memorized.
MONTH-END MARKETING MEETING
It was Da-reum.
Will you really be okay
going home alone?
You're here for work.
Do your best
and win Master Im over, okay?
- Okay. Get home safe, Mom.
- I will.
- Get back safely, ma'am.
- Thank you, Mr. Kang.
- Take care of my daughter for me.
- Don't.
- Bye, Eun-jeong.
- Take care.
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
Get home safe.
I'm pleased that you want to learn
how to make these.
I've been doing it for over ten years
but I still find it tough.
Master Im always says
making knots is like
asceticism or meditation.
She did it all her life
and she says it's still hard.
Compared to her,
I barely learned how to walk.
Maybe I'm yet to be born.
Anyway, as you can see here
this is a braided cord,
and it's covered in braided threads.
I'll teach you
how to make a knot out of this.
You must want to get a feel.
Shall we sit over there?
I'll teach you the easiest one.
It's one of the basic knots
called dongsimgyeol.
- Dongsimgyeol.
First, make a knot loop.
Knot loops are these large holes.
Take the two strands that are hanging
and put them between
the second and third loops.
- Like this?
- That's perfect.
You're doing well.
And then...
This one...
This goes up and fold...
Do I fold this one or that one?
This... Hang on.
You did it wrong.
It's not like this.
- This goes in here.
- Oh, that one?
- That goes first?
- And then
you slip this in here.
- Oh, this...
- In here.
- In the middle.
- Wait. Like this?
It's done. Oh, like this?
TRAINING COMPLETION CEREMONY
We did it. It's done.
After making this myself
it looks extra pretty
and I'm so proud of it.
It does.
I get what she meant
when she said it merges with time.
I didn't know so much work
went into making such a small knot.
I tried to manage on my own.
Thank you.
It's fine.
Tell us if you need help
with anything.
All my fellow students have left.
I'm the last remaining successor.
If I were to quit too
this skill will die out.
Please persuade Master Im for me.
It's a matter of time
before we lose all the artisans.
The work is intense,
and we barely make a living.
Who would do this?
Factory-made or handmade
I just want people to know
about traditional knots.
Is this what you thought all along?
Master Im.
If that's how you think, leave.
Make knots at a factory
and make a fortune!
"Make a fortune"?
I'd have quit long ago
if that's what I wanted.
I do this
to keep the tradition alive.
We need all the help we can get.
I at least...
Why do you say
I'm wrong just because
I take a different approach
to protect it?
Ms. Da-reum.
Yes?
Can you come outside?
Give me a moment.
I stuck them in the fire earlier
and didn't want to eat them alone.
Roasted sweet potatoes.
I didn't know you like this.
Have a taste.
- It smells amazing.
- Watch out. It's hot.
Ms. Da-reum, are you all right?
Spit it out here.
Why is he holding out his hands?
No, it's fine.
Take your time. Don't hurt yourself.
Thank you.
Why is Mr. Kang so nice to me?
It reminds me of my grandma.
She used to roast me
sweet potatoes like this.
It must be nice...
to have a kind grandma
and a mother.
Thanks to you
I enjoyed today.
What did you enjoy?
Drinking with your mother.
My mom died when I was
a high-school senior.
I never got to do that.
You can scratch that
off your bucket list.
I can.
What about you?
Do you have a bucket list?
Sit in the front row at a concert?
Have a pet?
And to hear
someone say to me
that they're glad to have me around.
It's corny, isn't it?
I must've been by the fire
for too long.
It's hot.
- I'll take a stroll.
- Okay.
What about you?
Would you like
to come with me on a walk?
I have a feeling
I'll remember today for a long time.
Me too.
I'm glad that you were here...
with me.
You took something off
my bucket list.
Ms. Da-reum.
You told me before
that you joined Appello
because there was someone
you wanted to meet.
Yes, well...
That was true then.
What's going on?
Why is he asking me that?
Be honest with me today.
The person you wanted to meet.
Was it me?
Pardon?
Do you see me as a man?
Do you think
that I'm interested in you?
It's just us two here. We can be...
No, wait.
Just a moment.
Is that why you said
you were the CEO
and I was an employee
and tried to keep your distance?
Was that really the reason?
I know very well
that we can never be.
I know so well who you like.
I did what?
Who could that be?
Oh, well...
Who do I like?
You have a thing
for Director Lee Chan.
- What?
- For a long time.
What the...
Excuse me?
Don't you worry.
I'll guard your feelings for you.
I'm not prejudiced at all.
Wait, Ms. Da-reum.
All this while
you thought I liked men?
But you do.
Ms. Da-reum.
I'm not into men.
- What?
- Also...
there's this woman
I'm interested in right now.
What?
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
EPILOGUE
Shall we pull?
Oh, yes.
It's done.
Do you know how to do it now?
Try it yourself.
It's the first thing
we made together.
Was it called dongsimgyeol?
Why are you so surprised?
I'm not.
DONGSIMGYEOL KNOT
TO BE OF ONE HEART FOREVER
WISHES FOR ETERNAL LOVE AND PEACE
Who is the woman he's interested in?
- Let's go in my car.
- Come with me.
What's this plot twist?
"You're the woman I'm interested in."
Why can't you say it? Why?
How about we stay
by each other's side from now on?
Who did she go to see?
You're so handsome.
- Don't be with a guy like that.
- Mr. Kang.
It's okay to tell me
that you're not okay.
Subtitles by Eunjin Erica Kim
and Jennifer Jean Lim
Synced and corrected by
WEISSACHsubs